Welcome.
In this video, you will learn about how to use the ASIN Status Report to remove or
unenroll eligible ASINs in Canada and Mexico in the Remote Fulfillment by FBA program.
To
start, go to the Inventory menu in Seller Central and then select the Remote Fulfillment
with FBA option from the dropdown.
Click on Generate Report to generate the latest version
of the report.
When the report is ready, the download button will be activated.
Click
on the button to view the report.
On the Enrollment tab of the report, you will be able to review
ASIN status on your entire FBA selection, including ASINs that are enabled, eligible and
enrolled, ineligible or requires action to enable.
You can unenroll enabled ASINs at
any point.
Simply filter to ASINs labeled as Enable on the Offer Status column.
Type
in No on the Enable Disable column under the destination marketplace you wish to unenroll
the offers from.
Save the changes in your file and go back to the Manage Your Remote Fulfillment
ASINs page.
Click on the Choose File button.
Select the ASIN Status Report file you just
saved and upload it back into our system.
Once the upload is completed successfully,
check under Results to make sure there are zero errors.
The select ASINs will be unenrolled
in chosen marketplaces within 24 hours.
In the future, if you want to reactivate those
ASINs, simply download the latest report again and type in Yes in the Enable Disable column
under the intended marketplaces.
Upload your saved report and your offers will be reactivated
or re-enrolled within 24 hours.
Thank you and happy selling!